

CONTACT

Address

236, Sai Shraddh Palace, Indore

Phone

+91 9977696202

Email

indrapal.singh1137@gmail.com

SKILLS

HTML 5

CSS₃

Tailwind css

Bootstrap

Js

jQuery

Photoshop

Figma

Adobe Xd

React UI

INDRAPAL SINGH JATAV

Sr. UI/UX DESIGNER

ABOUT ME

I have 4 years of experience in UI/UX Designer. I am always looking for self-improvement with new possibilities. In rapid and structured progression in the management of my work perseverance and leadership is the primary reason. My design style is clean, professional, and quick.

Every unique creation starts from imagination, followed by dedication. I worked in a challenging environment with honesty and commitment with a determination to apply my knowledge, skills and experience, and professional aptitudes for the organization's success.

Portfolio

https://indrapal1137.github.io/portfolio

EXPERIENCE

Hiecor Solution Sr. UI/UX designer	2022 - Present
Creative Thoughts Informatics Services Pvt Ltd UI/UX designer	2021-2022
Brainware Infosoft UI/UX designer	2020-2021
JIT Inspire UI/UX designer	2019-2020
Shiva Concept Solution Branch Manager & Trainer	2015-2019
E-Challan System (for Traffice police) indore Sr. Manager	2013-2015
NIIT Race Course & NIIT Vijay Nagar Indore Business Manager & Trainer	2010-2013

EDUCATION

Devi Ahilya Vishwavidyalaya Indore. Master of Business Administration (HR/IT)	2020-2023
Govt. Arts and Commerce College Indore. Becholer in arts	2017-2020
NIIT Delhi Professional Diploma in Software Engineering (GNIIT)	2008-2011